[{"Id":4,"Question":"What annotation is used above a JUnit test method?","Answers":[{"Text":"Test Development Decisions","IsCorrect":false},{"Text":"/* Test */","IsCorrect":false},{"Text":"// Test","IsCorrect":false},{"Text":"@Test","IsCorrect":true}],"Topic":"Assertions"},{"Id":5,"Question":"What should test methods return?","Answers":[{"Text":"1","IsCorrect":false},{"Text":"-1","IsCorrect":false},{"Text":"any integer","IsCorrect":false},{"Text":"void","IsCorrect":true}],"Topic":"Assertions"},{"Id":6,"Question":"How many arguments should a test method take?","Answers":[{"Text":"2","IsCorrect":false},{"Text":"At least 1","IsCorrect":false},{"Text":"0","IsCorrect":true},{"Text":"Exactly 1","IsCorrect":false}],"Topic":"Assertions"},{"Id":7,"Question":"Select all good unit test design approaches","Answers":[{"Text":"test the output of a method","IsCorrect":true},{"Text":"test boundary conditions","IsCorrect":true},{"Text":"test edge cases","IsCorrect":true},{"Text":"test error conditions","IsCorrect":true}],"Topic":"Assertions"},{"Id":8,"Question":"complexity of: n log n \u002B 5 log n \u002B 3n \u002B 5","Answers":[{"Text":"ON log N","IsCorrect":true},{"Text":"O3N","IsCorrect":false},{"Text":"ON","IsCorrect":false},{"Text":"O6 log N","IsCorrect":false}],"Topic":"Complexity"},{"Id":9,"Question":"complexity of: n^2 \u002B n log n - 2n","Answers":[{"Text":"ON^2","IsCorrect":true},{"Text":"ON log N","IsCorrect":false},{"Text":"ON","IsCorrect":false},{"Text":"O2N","IsCorrect":false}],"Topic":"Complexity"},{"Id":10,"Question":"Simplify 34 in Big-O notation","Answers":[{"Text":"O(N)","IsCorrect":false},{"Text":"O(1)","IsCorrect":true}],"Topic":"Complexity"},{"Id":11,"Question":"complexity of: log n \u002B 5","Answers":[{"Text":"O(5)","IsCorrect":false},{"Text":"O(1)","IsCorrect":false},{"Text":"O(N)","IsCorrect":false},{"Text":"O(log N)","IsCorrect":true}],"Topic":"Complexity"},{"Id":12,"Question":"complexity of: n^3 \u002B 2^n \u002B 100","Answers":[{"Text":"O(1)","IsCorrect":false},{"Text":"O(N^3)","IsCorrect":false},{"Text":"O(2^N)","IsCorrect":true},{"Text":"O(N^3 \u002B 2^N)","IsCorrect":false}],"Topic":"Complexity"},{"Id":13,"Question":"What is the complexity of reading a book stat to end?","Answers":[{"Text":"O(N^2)","IsCorrect":false},{"Text":"O(log N)","IsCorrect":false},{"Text":"O(N)","IsCorrect":true},{"Text":"O(1)","IsCorrect":false}],"Topic":"Complexity"},{"Id":14,"Question":"Select all Java primitives that count towards Big-O abstraction","Answers":[{"Text":"assignment","IsCorrect":true},{"Text":"calling a method","IsCorrect":true},{"Text":"indexing into an array","IsCorrect":true},{"Text":"the name of a variable","IsCorrect":false},{"Text":"comparison","IsCorrect":true}],"Topic":"Complexity"}]